Do not panic.
Remain in formation.
Keep your mounts as long as you can.
These men mean to see you dead.
They will fight savagely.
As will we. my lord.
Green fucking boys!
What of the kings guard?
Take heart. beesbury. I
will handle the kings guard.
Their oath forbids them to
harm a prince of the blood.
Is that honorable. your grace?
The gods will let us know.
Mother loved you best?
Shame.
No man fights so fierce as
one neglected by his mother.
Be vigilant.
Don't die.
Ser.
My Lance. squire.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
You best be here when I get back.
Rob me. and I'll hunt
you down with dogs.
Woof!
May the seven bear witness to
our solemn and bloody offering.
May they peer inside our
mortal hearts and find the truth.
May the warrior Grant
victory to the innocent...
And reveal the guilty in their falseness.
May death sustain life.
Up! Up! Go!
Hyah!
Fuck!
Ma... ma...
Ma...
I'm sorry.
Don't!
What the fuck are you doing?
He's got a seal.
He's dying.
If we can get him off the
hill. might someone pay us
for his ransom. Quick!
Fuck!
Do you know any words?
What's that mean?
You see. when these bloody highborn
spoil. you gotta say words for them.
- Why?
- So they don't end up
in no hell with the rest of us.
I don't know any words.
Right. Check his mouth.
I know a witch who
pays copper for teeth.
I am your queen!
Wipe my arse. liege.
What?
You never seen a man die before?
Yeah.
But not like that.
He was crying for his mother.
Yeah. what's she gonna do?
Lift the fucking horse off his legs?
Shit. come on.
Right. come on.
Come on.
I just don't know why we're in
such a rush to leave anymore.
The war is over. The
black dragon is dead.
Ferret said we're all
to get free bread now.
Are you stupid?
Nothing's over.
Don't you remember when
pudding killed Cedric's little brother?
- That was an accident.
- Aye.
And we all figured that'd be the end to it.
only for Cedric to come back a year later
and near burn down half of
flea bottom trying to kill pudding.
No one forgets shit.
You hurt someone. they hurt you back.
If you want to stay. fine.
But flea bottom is full
up on people hurting.
It's tinder waiting to catch.
Stay calm now.
You'll be alright.
Rafe.
Dunk.
What's in the bag?
Rats.
Rats!
Let's see 'em. then.
Fucking cunt!
You shouldn't have done that.
You know what alester's like.
Aye. and the evil bastard was
about to steal our shit. so I stole his.
That's not what I meant.
Is that not what you meant?
I'm doing him a favor.
This ale tastes as sour
as the queen's own brew.
Come on.
We'll all be plundering
that tomb for a dragon's age.
Hey!
Daemon's rebellion is over.
Take your blackfyre leather elsewhere.
Is it enough?
It's enough.
Hey. don't lose your nerve now.
The shit part's done.
I know.
We'll be sailing off into
all kinds of adventures.
- Don't you want that?
- I do.
I just...
What?
What if the free cities
are no better than here?
What if they're worse?
Then we'll go someplace else.
What if it's all shit?
Every place? What if
this is the best there is?
That would be quite sad.
And what if my mother
comes back for me?
I'm not stupid. I know she's dead.
But what if she's just trying to
get away from wherever she is?
Like we are?
If I leave. then how will she find me?
You are fucking stupid sometimes.
If your mother was alive.
she's not coming back for you.
You don't know that.
I know I never got
nothin' by waiting around.
You want a family?
Go out there. get a family.
I just want to be with you.
'Cause you love me.
Yeah.
Well...
I love you too. don't I?
And I'm going.
So. you best be coming with me.
This city is too small for us. dunk.
Let's show her our arse.
Right. come on. dunk.
Dunk. get a move on.
Two fares to the free cities.
What? Our silver don't spend?
Price is double.
You're not the only ones who
mean to get the fuck out of here.
- Right. Move!
- Wait. get off me!
Rafe.
Fuck!
- I suppose you're happy.
- What?
You've got plenty of time to wait
around for your dead mother now.
I'm sorry.
We'll find a way.
You got quick hands. girl.
I used to have quick hands.
I'll have me ale-skin back.
I sold it.
No! No. no.
We can get it back.
What's that?
Fuck off! Give it back.
Give it back.
Holding out on us.
That's ours.
Little gutter rats don't have silver.
Only little thieves.
We didn't thieve
nothing. We earned that.
Stealing from dead
nobles is still stealing.
And what's stealing from us?
- That's life.
- Yeah.
Come on.
Rafe. let's go.
Rafe!
Go on.
Rafe.
You little cunt.
No!
Fuck!
Stick him.
In the name of the mother!
Leave that boy be!
Get out of my way!
I'm sorry.
Maybe I'll have some of those apples.
- Yes... - You old fool.
- Sorry. I'm sorry.
Hey. boys. Did you miss me? Yeah.
You old fool!
Get up.
Come on!
Aerion!
My boy! My boy!
Get up.
Get up. ser!
Get up. dunk!
Yield.
Yield!
Get up. Get up. ser.
He's dead!
It's over!
Get up. ser!
Get up!
Get up. ser Duncan!
Get up. ser. Get up!
Get up.
Wait!
Up! Up! Up! Up!
I yield. I yield.
Tell him! Tell him!
Tell him!
I...
I withdraw my accusation.
That's it.
Come on.
Steady now.
I'll have to cut that mail off you.
The others.
Has anyone died?
Beesbury and hardyng.
in the first charge.
Gods be good.
The Lance point drove
the rings deep into his flesh.
One moment. I felt drunk.
The next. like I'm dying.
We'll get drunk. then
we'll pour boiling oil on it.
That's how the maesters do it.
Wine. Not oil.
Oil will kill him.
I'll send maester yormwell
to have a look at him
when he's done tending to my brother.
Your grace.
I am your man.
Please. Your man.
I need good men. ser Duncan.
The realm.
Ser raymun. my helm.
if you would be so kind.
- At once. your grace.
- Alright.
You're alright. You're alright.
Visor's... visor's cracked.
My fingers feel...
Fingers feel like wood.
Goodman pate.
A hand.
The helm. it's crushed
down the back. your grace.
It's smashed into the gorget.
My brother's mace. most like.
He's strong.
Gods be good.
No.
No. no! No.
No. no. your grace. Your grace.
Your grace. get up. ser.
Get up. ser! No!
No!
Please!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Get up!
I'm sorry.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-